This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cover path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Desperate to join the ranks of Sheiky the Golden Lion,
the Amigo Pirate stormed Consorn Island to capture the pirate's escaped giant beetle.
You have only two options here. Give us the beetle or die.
Look, I already tried. The beetle doesn't want to join a pirate crew.
So just leave him alone.
You got the wrong idea, idiot!
We're here to take that beetle to prison or not make friends with him!
It's there.
A rare, fire, fire, fire!
No!
I admire your elastic nature, but you must pay the price.
Comeuppance, senora.
A special presentation related to the movie,
The Fierce Onslaught of the Amigo Pirates.
Come on!
It's not fair!
She's unbeatable!
You've now won 69 games in a row.
You're like some sort of prodigy, Robin.
Hmm.
I wonder.
This is a game of luck, and nobody's that lucky.
Oh, my.
Is that so?
Then you're accusing me of cheating, Frankie.
Maybe so.
So loud!
What was that noise?
It came from behind the mountain.
Do you think Nami and the others are okay?
I guess catching that beetle is tougher than they thought.
Instead of playing cards, why don't we go give him a hand?
Big grow?
They're related?
They don't look it.
Damn it! What is this thing? It keeps biting me, stupid NET!
There's no point in fighting. You can struggle as much as you like, but the more you do, the tighter the net will get.
To suffocate at such a young age.
What a true world. A real tragedy.
Correct me if I'm wrong, but you are the vice-capitan, which makes you responsible for this shameful situation.
I can explain. The giant beetle we're after is supposed to be the guardian of the island, right?
So the plan was just to give them a good scare, enough to get the beetle to come to their rescue.
But then that noisy rubber poop head got in the way.
A giant beetle? How strange. I thought we were looking for a large needle.
Why would Shiki need a giant needle? You never listen to what I tell you. It's a grande beetle, okay?
Hmm. Oh, well then. I wonder if the giant beetle I happen to pass on the way here is the same Juan we're looking for.
What?
Oh, no. You've got to hide, boss. Boss! Can you hear me? Boss!
Where'd you see the beetle, big bro?
I think it was somewhere around there.
All right, then let's just...
Sure, we could saunter over and capture the stupid insect, but that's boring. It'd be more fun to give these yokels an ultimatum. Hand over the beetle or die. If I remember correctly, that was your original plan.
Why squander, your only good idea.
That was before we knew where the beetle was.
But, first off, it might behoove us to do away with these two ruffians who've been glaring at us with such hostility.
I'll give you a choice. Surrender yourselves to us now, or die by my net net food power, which would be muy malo.
Oh, such a tragic decision.
Ah, well. I'll wallow in your sorrows, swordsman.
Huh?
Hundred and eight caliber?
Yeah, nice try.
How surprising. And here I was about to nod off. Mucho sticcine.
Cut it.
But that is not all. Sticcine network!
What?
So darn sticky!
Tighten and tighten and tighten and speed!
Aw, jeez. Way to not get captured.
And what does our next rival do?
I'm a first-class chef, you weirdo bondage freak.
Ah.
Then something boiling hot seems appropriate, right, Colt?
Sure.
I don't really see how boiling your insides is gonna help you that much.
Well, that was certainly hot.
But no pain no gain.
Million boiling hot!
That's enough. Screw you and all your crappy nets.
Just let my friends go already!
Such loyal friendship does touch my heart.
Quailing to sacrifice his own life for them.
Namucho!
I am attacked!
What?
You cheater!
Huh?
Oh, come on!
Whoa, he just captured all three of them!
These guys are the real deal!
And there you have it.
To explain your means of confinement,
the swordsman is in my sticky net,
but there's also...
Iron...
Hot water...
And my favorite...
Little fuego!
I can transform any type of matter I ingest into a net.
Anything at all.
My capture rate, 120%.
I'm sure you'll regret challenging me.
But it is far too late for second thoughts now.
Many apologies.
So, I believe I'll leave this next part to you.
Make me proud and do your very worst.
Right.
You can count on it, big bro.
Two guys.
Your attention, please.
Coming from the East Blue,
I know your first reaction is to run and hide.
So, I'll appeal once again to your sense of survival.
Just give us the beetle,
or we'll slaughter every one of you.
All right.
I'm gonna start picking you off one by one from the inn.
I'd recommend speaking up if you don't wanna die.
That's enough!
Huh?
Hey!
Yoko, no!
Get back here!
Leave now!
Or I'll fight you!
Is that a navy coat?
They're sure recruiting them young these days.
Oh, no.
Senorita.
You threaten us with a bamboo sword.
Is the weight of your sorrow so great?
Shut up!
I can beat you jerks!
With any weapon I want!
No, don't do it!
Shoot her, right?
Yoko!
Ah!
Ahmed!
Sports, no!
I'm gonna take a guess that's Shiki's Big Beetle.
I didn't know it was that big.
And things were about to get interesting, too.
Take it down, Fox!
You show the bad guy!
Yeah, do it!
Go crazy, Fox!
Shoot it down!
Look at him go!
Awesome!
Careful, boss!
Big bro, how about some nets?
Such a letdown.
A thorough disappointment.
We were right on the cusp of a dreadfully beautiful and angelic inferno fueled by despair.
Now I'll never hear the symphony of their hopelessness.
Just use your damn nets!
Look at this annoying pest.
He's begging to be swatted.
Mucho burning nets!
Radiant fire!
No!
AND I'M LOSING!
It's the only trap right now.
No!
Oh!
Wait!
Whoa!
Buzz!
We got it!
Oh, Boss.
Man, I didn't think anyone could beat Boss.
There's no other way. Come on, please, Fabre.
The only way to save the island is to let them take Boss.
You're the mayor. Now make a decision.
Yoko, I'm sorry.
What should I do?
Dad, what would you do?
I can't surrender.
I'm here, Boss.
Huh?
Wait, where are you going?
Are you...
No! That's not what I want!
I can't.
No!
Boss!
Hey, Mayor Fabre.
What's Boss doing?
He must have...
He must have understood our feelings.
He heard how scared we were,
and now he's trying to save us by sacrificing himself.
No!
Thank you.
Hey there, it's okay.
Don't be afraid.
You've got cuts and bruises all over.
But it'll be fine.
Just take it easy.
I'll get you fixed up.
You'll see.
I promise you can trust me.
No!
Music to my ears.
Sad, lovely music.
Thank you for your grief, Senorita.
That was too easy.
That her anguish made it worth it.
Come in and get cozy.
With this beetle in our clutches, Shiki's gonna welcome us into his crew with open arms.
Hey, beetle!
Hold on!
I said stop!
I know you can hear me!
Nice try, but you're not taking the easy way out.
Not with these bastards.
Hear me, beetle?
You're not going anywhere until you fight me, damn it!
And don't act like you don't remember.
You can't back out of our promise!
Really, pirate?
Hey, what the hell's your problem?
He was just trying to sacrifice himself.
Can't you say he was trying to help us?
Shut up!
I don't give a damn about that!
All I want is to fight that giant beetle!
Is that it?
Jeez, he's hopeless.
Got a problem with that?
This is so awful.
This can't be happening.
I want Buzz to stay here with me!
Aw, Yoko.
You can't take him!
I won't let you!
He has to stay here!
There's nothing like a crying little girl to really open your eyes.
Put me down.
You're completely right, Yoko.
I'm sorry we were too scared to make the right decision earlier.
We were dumb enough to think we'd be better off letting them take Boss!
I'm ashamed it even crossed our minds.
Boss is like family to us, and we all love him!
As much as this island!
And, and, and, and no way are we gonna let!
Scum like you lot, take him from us!
Yeah!
Oh, now this is just pathetic.
Some scrappy ninja turns on the waterworks and you go loco?
It's like a melodrama.
To make me sick.
Death is their only option.
Underdogs ready to be put down.
So sad.
Wait, is that...
Huh?
It's happening!
Boss is shedding his skin!
Oh!
Ahh!
Whoa!
S sabeayıo!
Huh?
Argh!
How funny is that?
That Tom Beetle killing his own allies.
Boss!
What's wrong?
No, Boss.
This is awful.
It must have been too soon for him to mold.
I do not claim to be an entomologist, but you didn't finish molding.
How heartbreaking.
You have my pity.
Your screaming and crying won't do any good.
No one's gonna save you whining peasants now that we got your guardian angel.
The fight's not over yet.
Huh?
Gay?
You didn't risk your life for nothing.
We'll save your friends, Boss.
We owe you that much.
Leave everything to us.
Well, the fun's over.
It's time to get serious.
In hopes of saving the giant beetle and protecting Little East Blue, its citizens follow Nami's secret clan and take to the island's labyrinth-like caves.
Meanwhile, Luffy chases after Largo, but finds himself thwarted when Largo transforms his entire body into a net.
On the next One Piece, a special presentation related to the movie.
The battle is on.
Luffy versus Largo.
I am the king of the pirates.